let quiz = [
    {
        question: "4x + 3 = 19",
        option: [
            "x = -5",
            "x = 3",
            "x = 2",
            "x = 4",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "3x - 5 = 10",
        option: [
            "x = 5",
            "x = -2",
            "x = 1",
            "x = 0",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "3x = -15",
        option: [
            "x = 1",
            "x = 4",
            "x = -5",
            "x = 5",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "14x / 4 = 7",
        option: [
            "x = 4",
            "x = 3",
            "x = 2",
            "x = 1",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "2x + 3 + 4x = 21",
        option: [
            "x = 1",
            "x = 3",
            "x = -3",
            "x = -1",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "7x * 7 = 49",
        option: ["x = 1", "x = 2", "x = 6", "x = 7"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "18 / 3x = 2",
        option: [
            "x = -2",
            "x = 3",
            "x = -4",
            "x = 4",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "x + 3x = 24",
        option: ["x = 6", "x = -7", "x = 9", "x = -5"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "50 / 2 + x = 5",
        option: ["x = 7", "x = 4", "x = 8", "x = 2"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "2x - 2 = 10",
        option: ["x = 4", "x = 6", "x = 0", "x = -8"],
        answer: 2,
    },
];